<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<site>
	<client id="1" name="AIR FRANCE">
		<data>
			<texts>
				<page name="The Product">
					<text><![CDATA[Air France faces an ongoing, intensified competitive pressure - from the low cost companies that provide ultra-competitive pricing and low service, to the major airlines that all compete on increasingly specialised “service” claims: size of seats, entertainment systems etc. In order to gain customer preference and establish unquestionable superiority, we had to redefine the added value of Air France.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="The Challenge">
					<text><![CDATA[Air France faces an ongoing, intensified competitive pressure - from the low cost companies that provide ultra-competitive pricing and low service, to the major airlines that all compete on increasingly specialised “service” claims: size of seats, entertainment systems etc. In order to gain customer preference and establish unquestionable superiority, we had to redefine the added value of Air France.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="The CBI">
					<text><![CDATA[We moved Air France from simply an airline… to a well-being provider. In recent years, flying had become a dreaded way to travel. We wanted to free flying from its constraints and annoyances, and make it a relaxing, enjoyable time for each passenger – on the ground and in the air. The brand would stand for the pleasure of travel and relaxation, and Air France would be the airline “Making the Sky the Best Place on Earth.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="Strategy">
					<text><![CDATA[The redefinition of Air France’s role had important consequences on the whole airline strategy. Air France launched new e-services to increase comfort and well-being, both before and in flight, and launched the NEV (nouvel espace voyageur) flat beds and improved entertainment video services on board. A new version of the in-flight magazine was developed with a focus on the well-being promise and the Air France “soundtrack” for planes was redesigned by Euro RSCG to create a more relaxing and luxurious atmosphere. In October 2008, we launched a new advertising campaign in the 100+ markets where Air France is present around the world.  The campaign was shot by award-winning photographer Camilla Akrans, and the visuals illustrate the essential aspects of the Air France passenger experience: quality, tranquility, refinement and well-being.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="Results">
					<text><![CDATA[Business results over the past few years have been phenomenal - the initial campaign tested incredibly positively with 70% of Americans recalling Air France communications (vs. 45% norm) and a higher likeability score than the TNS norm (75 vs. 70).  The campaign also won several advertising awards including an Epica Silver Award, Meribel Winner for the Transport category (overall and Europe) and winner in the Soundtrack category, plus the Grand Prix Outdoor. The impact of the new global campaign has yet to be wholly felt, but early qualitative testing already shows that consumers feel the arresting visuals effectively build an image of an airline that puts quality of service first and evokes a “special, intimate experience.]]></text>
				</page>
			</texts>
			<media>
				<photos>
					<photo src="air_france_1" />
					<photo src="air_france_2" />
					<photo src="air_france_3" />
					<photo src="air_france_4" />
				</photos>
				<videos>
					<video src="air_france_1" />
					<video src="air_france_2" />
				</videos>
			</media>
		</data>										
	</client>	
	<client id="2" name="EBAY">
		<data>
			<texts>
				<page name="The Product">
					<text><![CDATA[eBay is the first auction and shopping website, where millions of people and businesses buy and sell goods and services worldwide.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="The Challenge">
					<text><![CDATA[In France, eBay is a great brand at a turning point in its history. It enjoys high brand awareness and a good brand image but it is still widely regarded as a place for specialists and collectors.  eBay had to get into people’s minds for more casual and everyday shopping.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="The CBI">
					<text><![CDATA[The idea was to put eBay’s own ad space up for auction on the eBay site and let the winners of the auction advertise on TV for the item they were trying to sell on eBay.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="Strategy">
					<text><![CDATA[The TV campaign we developed for eBay is extremely innovative but builds on a very simple idea: we put the people that make eBay at the centre of our communication strategy. The campaign ran in three phases. First, a mysterious 30-second spot told people that eBay was putting its advertising space up for auction.  People were invited to log on to eBay and bid for the opportunity to shoot a proper TV commercial of the item they were selling on eBay.  At the end of the first week we had 10 ‘sellers’ with 10 items.  We shot them the following week and aired the films as soon as possible after they were produced. Just two weeks after the teaser TVC, the first film of an auction winner aired!]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="Results">
					<text><![CDATA[This campaign has been a real business success. On the day of the campaign launch, the French eBay site saw its audience peak at the highest point since its creation. By the end of the campaign, unique visitors had increased by an astonishing 10% (one million additional unique users) with an increase in purchase intention of 30% among non-eBay users. Post test results reflect the incredible impact of the campaign.  It has been ranked in the top 10 most efficient campaigns in France, and its specific recognition has been measured at eight times the TV norm. Plus, the campaign is highly recognised creatively and has been awarded a Yellow Pencil at D&AD, a Gold medal at the 2008 Jay Chiat Planning Awards and the Gold Medal at the Montreux International Ad Festival.  It won in the Online Services Category at the Advertising Grand Prix and in the Best Use of Media category at the Media Grand Prix.  To top it off, it was ranked the fourth most awarded Alternative & Innovative Media campaign of 2008 according to The Big Won report.]]></text>
				</page>
			</texts>
			<media>
				<videos>
					<video src="ebay_1" />
					<video src="ebay_2" />
					<video src="ebay_3" />
					<video src="ebay_4" />
					<video src="ebay_5" />
					<video src="ebay_44" />
				</videos>
			</media>
		</data>										
	</client>	
	<client id="3" name="JAGUAR XF">
		<data>
			<texts>
				<page name="The Product">
					<text><![CDATA[Since the company was founded in 1922, Jaguar has evolved from the production of motorcycle sidecars to become one of the world's leading designers and manufacturers luxury sports and sports saloon cars.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="The Challenge">
					<text><![CDATA[The first expression of the strategy was the 'Gorgeous' campaign, which in 2005 relaunched the brand and supported the launch of the new XK sports car.  This activity defied all category conventions and successfully repositioned the brand as a global luxury brand. Building on this foundation the 2007 campaign for the launch of the new XF brought to life the brand's values of innovative design, performance and craftsmanship, appealing to Jaguar's audience of modern connoisseurs, people for whom experience, luxury and speed are some of life's great pleasures. This integrated global campaign has created the benchmark in innovative 360-degrees communications.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="The CBI">
					<text><![CDATA[The luxury automotive landscape was incredibly intense and getting louder with everyone occupying the same terrain - we needed to dare to break the codes of the category. We encapsulated our new approach to luxury car communication for Jaguar through the idea of 'New fashioned luxury' which aimed to reignite passion for Jaguar and establish it as a modern luxury brand.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="Strategy">
					<text><![CDATA[The first expression of the strategy was the 'Gorgeous' campaign, which in 2005 relaunched the brand and supported the launch of the new XK sports car.  This activity defied all category conventions and successfully repositioned the brand as a global luxury brand. Building on this foundation the 2007 campaign for the launch of the new XF brought to life the brand's values of innovative design, performance and craftsmanship, appealing to Jaguar's audience of modern connoisseurs, people for whom experience, luxury and speed are some of life's great pleasures. This integrated global campaign has created the benchmark in innovative 360-degrees communications.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="Results">
					<text><![CDATA[By the end of February 2008 Jaguar had 12,000 pre-registrations for the new XF. This was significantly above target and a great achievement for a car that would not be available in dealerships until the end of March 2008. Ian Callum, head of design, said that for the first time in his career, his vision for his cars is being expressed in communications for the cars. By working in true partnership with this client, we've created an alignment between marketer and designer that had heretofore not existed.]]></text>
				</page>
			</texts>
			<media>
				<videos>
					<video src="jaguar_xf_1" />
				</videos>
			</media>
		</data>										
	</client>	
	<client id="4" name="THE SUN">
		<data>
			<texts>
				<page name="The Product">
					<text><![CDATA[The Sun newspaper is the most famous British tabloid, as well as the world’s biggest selling English language daily newspaper.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="The Challenge">
					<text><![CDATA[The Sun has a history of influencing the UK political landscape and championing the views of its readers.  In 1992, The Sun was so convinced of its contribution to the Conservative Party's victory that it declared on the front page, 'IT WAS THE SUN WOT WON IT'.  Our challenge was to highlight The Sun’s political clout, specifically by reminding Britain of the promise that Gordon Brown made to give the UK public a referendum on Europe.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="The CBI">
					<text><![CDATA[Our idea was simple: the best way to provoke the biggest reaction on the issue was to target the Prime Minister, Gordon Brown, directly.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="Strategy">
					<text><![CDATA[We developed an arresting visual for the campaign, featuring the iconic image of Churchill outside Number 10, but now sporting Gordon Brown’s superimposed face and pictured giving two fingers to Britain. The headline read: 'Europe. Never have so few decided so much for so many.' The creative ran as the front page of the newspaper and kickstarted a much wider campaign involving ongoing editorial coverage in The Sun, projections onto the Houses of Parliament and a huge ambient media campaign in Bournemouth on the first day of the Labour Party conference.]]></text>
				</page>
				<page name="Results">
					<text><![CDATA[The idea captured the imagination of the readers, and interaction between Sun readers and the newspaper/website was huge with over 100,000 people signing up to a petition calling for an EU Referendum.  The campaign also generated a vast amount of PR coverage, including national TV news – BBC News 24, Sky News, BBC Breakfast - as well as Radio 4's The Today Programme, the most popular programme on the nation’s most highly respected and influential radio station.]]></text>
				</page>
			</texts>
			<media>
				<photos>
					<photo src="the_sun_1" />
				</photos>
				<videos>
					<video src="the_sun_1" />
				</videos>
			</media>
		</data>										
	</client>
</site>